[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Goldfinger, James Bond hates this quartet, popular at the time the movie was produced.", "correct_answer": "The Beatles", "incorrect_answers": ["The Yardbirds", "The Ronettes", "The Temptations"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Carrot tops are poisonous to humans, even in small quantities.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Evil Dead 2, the main character is spared no embarrassment. At a certain point he feels he is really losing his mind and sees what set-up animal laughing at him?", "correct_answer": "Moose", "incorrect_answers": ["Raven", "Lion", "Lynx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can a zebra be ridden if trained properly?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This famous bra brand was introduced to the USA in May 1994.  It started selling at a rate of one every 15 seconds at the initial retail price of $26.", "correct_answer": "Wonderbra", "incorrect_answers": ["Bali", "La Perla", "Victorias Secret"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What pet name were Warner and Elle using for each other in the 2001 American comedy Legally Blonde?", "correct_answer": "Pooh Bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Bunny", "Kitty", "Cakes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which city does the action in the movie The Crow  take place?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Seattle", "New York", "Detroit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of MaryAnns song in The Fighting Temptations 2003 movie which Paulina points out to the church members as improper and devils music", "correct_answer": "Do It To Me Again", "incorrect_answers": ["Turn Me On", "You Make Me Hot", "Yours From Head To Toe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A very common greeting in India is namaste or namaskar. What does it mean?", "correct_answer": "I bow  to you.", "incorrect_answers": ["I pray your family is complete.", "May you be blessed.", "How are  you?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which letter of the alphabet is also the name of a popular computer programming language?", "correct_answer": "C", "incorrect_answers": ["E", "B", "A"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the biggest extinct volcano in Ecuador, situated in the Andes mountain.", "correct_answer": "Chimborazo", "incorrect_answers": ["Ojos Del Salado", "Llullaillaco", "Cotopaxi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Crow, which of these is the bar of Top Dollar, one of Eric and Shellys murderers?", "correct_answer": "Club Trash", "incorrect_answers": ["The Split Crow", "Bloody Nails", "Thrash Party"]}]